This week's Yoru-kun
Good evening, Daikoku-san and Daiyuu-san.
This week, I did squats for my health.
But I could only do 4 squats.
My body is very heavy.
I'll see you all in the next couple of weeks.
Nighttime and Idols
Well, it's almost the end of the show.
So early!
Any news from Oguro-san? Thank you very much. As I mentioned earlier, Yuzuki's Room, which is held every Monday, will hold a festival this year as well.
Yuzuki's Room will hold a festival again this year.
On June 3, Yuzuki's Room Fes 2023 will be held at ZEPP Shinjuku in Tokyo.
This is a two-part event.
I see!
I see. Orca will be in both parts,
The first part will be x-shoujo-tai, myself, Mai Haruna, and Luna Naito,
Yes.
There is also a unit called "Rumi Glo" that you can only see here.
The second part is Team Shachi,
Iginari Tohoku San-chan, and Ame-Flahi.
In both parts of the event, all of the STAPLARA students came to perform in the welcome room,
We are very happy to have so many STAPLA members coming to the event.
Team Shachi's one-man live concert is also scheduled.
Saturday, July 22nd at Nagoya Castle,
Orca will be held at Nagoya Castle on Saturday, July 22.
Here he comes. Killer Whale.
This is Killer Whale.
This is a big one-man show that we do every year,
I really want as many people as possible to see it.
I really want as many people as possible to see it and receive my thoughts.
I want as many people as possible to see the show and receive my thoughts and feelings,
I want to express my gratitude and love to everyone.
I want to convey my feelings more fully than ever before.
And I am a woman who wants something in return,
I hope that you will come to the show and repay me with your passion.
I would like to invite people who have never been to a Team Shachi concert before,
If you have never been to a Team Shachi concert, or if you have not been recently, but would like to go to one, please come and join us,
Please join us at the Orca Restaurant.
And I'd like to repeat this again,
Every Monday night at 9:00 p.m.
Team Orca's YouTube channel.
Dizky's Room.
This is also a bit of a loose project,
But it's also about the friendly atmosphere with my roommates,
We always deliver live in a warm and friendly atmosphere.
It's a lot of fun, and you can blow away your daily stress,
You can watch it for free,
You can watch it for free. Please watch it.
And one more thing.
A place for me to shine.
Oh, I'm sorry. This one is really just a little bit.
It's a telecast every Monday night at 7 p.m. on Teresa Video, so it will be available.
It's called "Kawakami Akira's One Hundo's Girl,
Every week, J.Seph will be the MC, and the guest will change every week,
I will be in charge of the second week.
I will be in charge for the second week.
You can enjoy Yuzuki to the fullest.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, Mondays are heavy.
Heavy!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It really is.
Not even for a second more.
Please finish your bath already.
That's what I mean.
No bathroom breaks, no bath breaks.
I hope you'll be able to enjoy me all the way through.
So please look forward to Monday.
I look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Last but not least, Mr. Yoguro.
I would like to give you a present from the Night Army, tea to cheer you up!
Delicious!
Tea.
Thank you very much. Do you drink tea?
Usually? I have a cat's tongue. I don't drink hot tea.
I see. It smells soft and minty.
It smells good. I'll have some.
What do you think?
Just right.
Oh, Mom!
Delicious! It's warming!
Oh, thank goodness!
Thank you very much.
And last but not least...
Look so cute for the camera!
She's cute when she closes.
I have to say it myself.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.It was a lot of fun.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you so much!
I love you all!
That's all for now.
Thank you very much!
This program was made possible by my friend Osamu Yabao,
Osamu, Ujicha Panda, Toshikazu
Toshikazu-chan,
Yabao,
Golipon-san.
Thank you very much.